<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fall '23 Week 1 :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week01/index.html</link><description>Ed Discussion This video was recorded before I decided to switch to Ed Discussion instead of using Discord. All discussions of “Discord” can be applied to “Ed Discussion” instead. Sorry for the confusion! - Russ
Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week one announcements for CIS 527 and CC 510. In Fall 2023, my name is Russ Feldhausen. I’ll be your instructor for this semester, my contact information can be found here. It’s also on the syllabus. It’s also on the cannabis page. Feel free to reach out to me if you have any questions or concerns at all in this class. I also have one teaching assistant this semester, Matt Schwartz, Matt is going to be working with me to help you if you have any questions on the labs, he’s also going to be helping me with doing some of the grading Matt did this class last year, I believe. So he’s pretty familiar with a lot of the content. And he’s going to be working right alongside you to check all the labs for me. So if you have any questions, feel free to reach out to either of us, we’re happy to help. In this course, just like a lot of courses, it’s built with gated modules on canvas. There’s one module due every other week in this class, so please check the due dates very carefully. Each module includes a lab assignment, that lab assignment requires a live grading portion, which means you’ll work with either Matt or myself via zoom, so that we can grade your work, it means that this is a very labor intensive class. So please be aware of that. We’re also going to have some discussions throughout the semester. So you’ll either have a recorded video to watch, or I’ll bring in a guest speaker and you’ll have the opportunity to join a live zoom and speak with one of our guest speakers. And then finally, at the end of the semester, we’ll have a final project.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week01/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/></channel></rss>