<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>July 27, 2020 :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200727/index.html</link><description>Resources Slides Video Script Good morning and welcome to the last weekly announcements video for CIS 527 for summer 2020. I’m really excited to see the end of the semester and I hope you are too. Here’s a few quick things to keep in mind for this week. First off lab seven was due last Friday. So if you haven’t completed and turned in lab seven, make sure you do that ASAP. If you look on Piazza, there’s information about how to turn in lab seven completely offline so you don’t have to get any live grading done. But if you’re having trouble with it, you can always schedule a live grading time especially if you want us to look at what you’re doing and see if we can give you at least partial credit for it. So please make sure you do that. If you’ve already turned in lab seven, BreAnn went through and graded almost all of it this weekend. So hopefully you should see some notes on Canvas very shortly. If you haven’t heard back from her yet, you should be very soon. If you have gotten an email from her especially about task five on GitLab, please make sure you respond to that ASAP so that we can get the permissions we need so we can test task five of lab seven on GitLab. Also, don’t forget the final project proposal was due Friday, I believe I got a final project proposal from most everybody in the class. So that’s really great. I posted comments and feedback on those so you can check that out on Canvas anytime. Also, don’t forget the week six discussion response for Gary Pratt K-State CIO is due today. So you can go out to Canvas and find the discussion prompt for that. And also, final project presentations are coming up this week. So if you haven’t scheduled your time for your final project presentation, please do so now. My Friday afternoon is already almost completely booked up. So make sure you’re looking at my calendar and planning ahead accordingly. Just because you get it done on Friday doesn’t mean you may have time to present it if you haven’t scheduled a time, so don’t forget to do that. I generally prefer presentations on Thursday and Friday of this week. But if you think you’ll get done sooner you can schedule earlier than that. So check our Calendly availability and see when we’re available. Also, please bear in mind that BreAnn doesn’t have any official availability right; now she started her full time job this week. But she will be doing some stuff in the weekends and generally following up with this class when she has time. So mostly if you need Calendly availability, it will be on my calendar for the rest of this week.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200727/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/></channel></rss>