<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Summer 2022 :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/index.html</link><description/><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Summer '22 Week 1</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week01/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week01/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week one Announcements video for system administration during summer 2022. My name is Russell Feldhausen. I’ll be your instructor for this course, my contact information is shown here. You can also find it on the syllabus and on the homepage on K-State canvas, it’s by far the best way to get a hold of me is to just email me. But as I discussed in the intro video, and as I’ll discuss here, for anything related to the course, please use discord, it’s a great place for us to chat and you should get some very quick responses from you there. So a little bit about the structure in the course.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 2</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week02/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week02/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week two announcements video for CIS 527 in summer 2022. So this week you should be finishing up lab one. Lab one grading is due tonight by 7pm. So if you haven’t scheduled a time to meet with me for grading, make sure you do that ASAP. I do have trainings on Monday afternoons from about one to three, I usually get done with those a little earlier. But it’s worth noting that at least half of my afternoon is taken up by another meeting. So make sure you schedule your schedule your grading times in advance so that you can get those in whenever they work for you. And of course, if you work from eight to five, let me know and I’ll make some time available in my calendar probably after 5pm. So around six or seven to get you taken care of coming up this week, you’ve got lab two quizzes, which are due on Friday. And then next week, you’ll be turning in lab two and the first discussion which is the week two discussion.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 3</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week03/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week03/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week three announcements video for CIS 527 in summer 2022. So this week you should be wrapping up lab two, which is due tonight at 7pm. I’ll talk about that briefly in just a second. You also should be working on the week two discussion questions and responses which are due tonight at 11:59pm. So make sure you leave enough time to watch that video, write your responses and respond to the question prompts there as well. This Friday, you’ll have the week three quizzes that are due and then next Monday, you’ll be turning in lab three, and also doing the week three discussion.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 4</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week04/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week04/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week for announcements video for CIS 527 in summer 2022. This week, you should be working on lab three, which is due today by 7pm. So make sure you getting that wrapped up and also that you have a time scheduled with me to get your grading done. I’ll talk about that in just a minute. You’re also should be working on the week three discussion, which is due tonight by 11:59pm. So make sure you watch the video, write some responses and also provide some new questions for our guests. This week, you’re working on week four. So we four quizzes are due Friday. And then the next lab which is lab four is due next Tuesday. We’re postponing it today to to the holiday on Monday, the July 4. So there is a lab that’s due next Tuesday, you’ll need to schedule a time with me to get that graded. But there is no discussion this week, we’re pushing off the discussion until week five. So you don’t have to worry about a discussion this week, just focusing on lab four.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 5</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week05/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week05/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week five Announcements video for CIS 527 in summer 2022. So this week, you should be wrapping up lab four, which is notoriously the hardest lab in this class, it is due today by 7pm. So make sure you get that done and schedule a grading time with me later today. So we can get that looked at. And then next week, you’re going to be shifting over to lab five, where we’re going to pivot from virtual machines on our system to actually working in the cloud. So Friday of the week, five quizzes are due and the next Monday, you’ll be turning in lab five, as well as the week five discussion.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 6</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week06/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week06/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week six Announcements video for CIS 527 in summer 2022. So this week, you should be wrapping up lab five, which is due today at 7pm. So make sure you get that done. Most of lab grading is really simple. And we’ll talk about that in just a minute. You should also be wrapping up the week five discussion, which is also due tonight by midnight, so make sure you get that done. This week, you’ll be working on Week Six content. So the week six quizzes are due Friday. And then lab six and the week six discussions are due next Monday.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 7</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week07/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week07/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week seven announcements video for CIS 527 In summer 2022. So we’re getting toward the end of the semester. So this week, don’t forget you got lab six due tonight by 7pm. So make sure you get that submitted, I’ve got most grading times available for students. But if you need more help or needed writing time, just let me know. It’s also available on Calendly. Like always, there’s a week six discussion that’s due tonight by 1159. So make sure you watch the video, respond to it and post some questions for our guest speaker. This week on Friday, you’ve got the week, seven quizzes that are due. And you also have your final project proposal that’s due, we’ll talk a little bit about the final project and the second. And then next Monday, lab seven, the last seven, the last lab in this class is due. And there’s also one more discussion that is due next Monday as well. I will be posting lab seven, hopefully later today. So you can get started on that.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 8</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week08/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week08/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the weekend Announcements video for CIS 527 In summer 2022. This week we should be wrapping everything up in the class. So you’ve got week seven discussion, which is due today by 1159. And then lab seven and the final project are due on Friday both by 1159. As well, you also should be receiving an email inviting you to complete a TEVAL for this course later today. So make sure you take care of your TEVALs. That information is really really helpful to me as I continue to improve and work on this course.</description></item></channel></rss>