<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/index.html</link><description>Course Introductory Material for CIS 527 Online</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:04:19 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Course Introduction</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/01-course-introduction/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/01-course-introduction/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Syllabus Video Script Welcome to CIS 527 - Enterprise System Administration and CC 510 - Computer Systems Administration. Even though these are two different courses in the catalog, they teach the same content and will use the same Canvas course. So, anywhere you see CIS 527 in this course, you can also mentally substitute CC 510 in its place.</description></item><item><title>Navigating Canvas &amp; YouTube</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/02-navigating-canvas-youtube/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/02-navigating-canvas-youtube/index.html</guid><description>Video Script This course makes extensive use of several features of Canvas which you may or may not have worked with before. To give you the best experience in this course, this video will briefly describe those features and the best way to access them.
When you first access the course on Canvas, you will be shown this homepage, with my contact information and any important information about the course. This is a quick, easy reference for you if you ever need to get in touch with me.</description></item><item><title>Where to Find Help</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/03-where-to-find-help/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/03-where-to-find-help/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides K-State IT Help Desk - Email helpdesk@ksu.edu Syllabus K-State Canvas Help Instructure Canvas Guides K-State Libraries K-State CS Support K-State CS Discord K-State CS Advising K-State Engineering Student Services K-State Office of Student Life K-State Report It Video Script As you work on the materials in this course, you may run into questions or problems and need assistance. This video reviews the various types of help available to you in this course.</description></item><item><title>What You'll Learn</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/04-what-youll-learn/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/04-what-youll-learn/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Why Circuit City Busted, While Best Buy Boomed Video Script Before you begin this course, here is a quick overview of what you’ll be learning and why it is important.
First, the labs. Lab 1 - Secure Workstations, is all about installing and configuring computers for your end users to use in a large organization. This is a great place to start in system administration, because it is very similar to working on your own, personal computer. You’ll install an operating system, learn about its various parts, and configure a secure and stable workstation. If you’ve taken my CIS 225 course, this is basically a review of a large portion of that material.</description></item><item><title>Fall 2025 Syllabus</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/05-syllabus/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/05-syllabus/index.html</guid><description>CIS 527 - Enterprise Systems Administration CC 510 - Computer Systems Administration Previous Versions
This syllabus covers both courses. They are taught using the same content.
Instructor Contact Information Instructor: Mr. Russell Feldhausen (russfeld AT ksu DOT edu) Office: DUE 2213, but I mostly work remotely from Kansas City, MO Phone: (785) 292-3121 (Call/Text) Website: https://russfeld.me Virtual Office Hours: By appointment via Zoom. Book time to meet with me Teaching Assistant Josh Barron (jrbarron AT ksu DOT edu) - Office Hours by appointment. Schedule a meeting at https://calendly.com/joshbarron2222 Preferred Methods of Communication: Email: Email is the official method of communication for this course. Any emails sent to the instructor regarding this course should be answered within one class day. Please use the official course email address: cis527-help@ksuemailprod.onmicrosoft.com Ed Discussion: For short questions and discussions of course content and assignments, Ed Discussion is preferred since questions can be asked once and answered for all students. Students are encouraged to post questions there and use that space for discussion, and the instructor will strive to answer questions there as well. Phone/Text: Emergencies only! I will do my best to respond as quickly as I can. Prerequisites CIS 527: CIS 300. CC 510: CC 310 or CIS 300. Students may enroll in CIS or CC courses only if they have earned a grade of C or better for each prerequisite to those courses.</description></item></channel></rss>