




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on CIS 527 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on CIS 527 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 10:53:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Course Introduction</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/01-course-introduction/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/01-course-introduction/index.html</guid>
      <description>Ed Discussion This video was recorded before I decided to switch to Ed Discussion instead of using Discord. All discussions of &amp;ldquo;Discord&amp;rdquo; can be applied to &amp;ldquo;Ed Discussion&amp;rdquo; instead. Sorry for the confusion! - Russ
Resources Slides Syllabus Video Script Welcome to CIS 527 - Enterprise System Administration and CC 510 - Computer Systems Administration. Even though these are two different courses in the catalog, they teach the same content and will use the same Canvas course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Canvas &amp; YouTube</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/02-navigating-canvas-youtube/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/02-navigating-canvas-youtube/index.html</guid>
      <description>Video Script This course makes extensive use of several features of Canvas which you may or may not have worked with before. To give you the best experience in this course, this video will briefly describe those features and the best way to access them.
When you first access the course on Canvas, you will be shown this homepage, with my contact information and any important information about the course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where to Find Help</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/03-where-to-find-help/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/03-where-to-find-help/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides K-State IT Help Desk - Email helpdesk@ksu.edu Syllabus K-State Canvas Help Instructure Canvas Guides K-State Libraries K-State CS Support K-State CS Discord K-State CS Advising K-State Engineering Student Services K-State Office of Student Life K-State Report It Video Script As you work on the materials in this course, you may run into questions or problems and need assistance. This video reviews the various types of help available to you in this course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What You&#39;ll Learn</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/04-what-youll-learn/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/04-what-youll-learn/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Why Circuit City Busted, While Best Buy Boomed Video Script Before you begin this course, here is a quick overview of what you&amp;rsquo;ll be learning and why it is important.
First, the labs. Lab 1 - Secure Workstations, is all about installing and configuring computers for your end users to use in a large organization. This is a great place to start in system administration, because it is very similar to working on your own, personal computer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2023 Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/05-syllabus/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/0-introduction/05-syllabus/index.html</guid>
      <description>CIS 527 - Enterprise Systems Administration CC 510 - Computer Systems Administration Previous Versions This syllabus covers both courses. They are taught using the same content.
Instructor Contact Information Instructor: Russell Feldhausen (russfeld AT ksu DOT edu)
I use he/him pronouns. Feel free to share your own pronouns with me, and I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to use them! Office: DUE 2213, but I mostly work remotely from Kansas City, MO Phone: (785) 292-3121 (Call/Text) Website: https://russfeld.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>