




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Secure Workstations on CIS 527 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Secure Workstations on CIS 527 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:53:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/01-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/01-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Operating System on Wikipedia Types of Operating Systems on Geeks for Geeks Understanding Operating Systems on GCF LearnFree GNU/Linux Naming Controversy on Wikipedia The Great Debate: Is it Linux or GNU/Linux? on How-To Geek Video Script Welcome to the first module in this class! Module 1 is all about creating secure workstations. In this module, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to install virtual machine software, install the operating systems we&amp;rsquo;ll be using in the class, and then configure several aspects of the operating systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assignment</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/02-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/02-assignment/</guid>
      <description>Warning This is the assignment page for Lab 1. It is placed before the rest of the module&amp;rsquo;s content so you may begin working on it as you review the content. Click Next below to continue to the rest of the module.
Lab 1 - Secure Workstations Instructions Create two virtual machines meeting the specifications given below. The best way to accomplish this is to treat this assignment like a checklist and check things off as you complete them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtualization &amp; VMware</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/03-virtualization-vmware/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/03-virtualization-vmware/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Virtualization on Wikipedia Virtualization Whitepaper from VMware Accessing VMware Software on CS Support Video Script In this class, we will be making heavy use of virtualization software to allow us to run multiple operating systems simultaneously on the same computer. This video provides a quick overview of what virtualization is and how it works.
First, a simple view of how a computer works. In essence, whenever you tell the computer to run a program, you are actually telling the operating system what to do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Users &amp; Groups</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/04-users-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/04-users-groups/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Working with user accounts and groups is one of the key tasks within system administration. Before we get to working directly within a system, here is some background information about users and groups to help you understand why they are so important.
Early computers did not have any concept of user accounts. If you had physical access to a machine and knew how to use it, you could.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 Overview &amp; Installation</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/05-windows-overview-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/05-windows-overview-installation/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides How to Get Windows 10 from Microsoft Azure Portal via CS Support How to Install VMware Tools from VMware Windows 10 Overview from Microsoft Microsoft Windows Version History from Wikipedia Windows 10 for Windows 7 Users from How-To Geek Windows 10 for Windows 8 Users from How-To Geek Windows 10 Help from Microsoft Windows 10 Wiki from Microsoft TechNet Windows 10 Architecture from Microsoft TechNet Windows 10 ISO Downloads from Microsoft Warning: May not work with keys from the Microsoft Imagine store!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/06-windows-powershell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/06-windows-powershell/</guid>
      <description>Resources Getting Started with Windows PowerShell from Microsoft PowerShell Documentation from Microsoft Sample PowerShell Scripts from Microsoft PowerShell Community Blog from Microsoft Hey, Scripting Guy! Blog from Microsoft (older content) Video Script Before digging too deep into Windows, let&amp;rsquo;s take some time to learn about one of its most powerful, and least used, features, the PowerShell command line interface. PowerShell is an update to the old Command Prompt terminal, which was a very limited version of the DOS terminal from decades ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 User Management</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/07-windows-user-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/07-windows-user-management/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides How to Manage Microsoft and User Accounts in Windows 10 from Windows Central How to Set Up and Configure User Accounts on Windows 10 from How-To Geek The Geek&amp;rsquo;s Way of Managing User Accounts and Groups in Windows from Digital Citizen Video Script Once you have installed Windows 10, the next step is to configure the user accounts and groups needed on the system. There are three major methods for configuring user accounts, and each give you access to different sets of features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 File Permissions</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/08-windows-file-permissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/08-windows-file-permissions/</guid>
      <description>Warning See the warning in the video script below for a correction that is not present in the video &amp;ndash;Russ
Resources File and Folder Permissions from Microsoft How to Understand Those Confusing Windows 7 File/Share Permissions from How-To Geek How to Take Ownership and Change Permissions of Files and Folders from Digital Citizen Advanced Security Audit Policy Settings from Microsoft Video Script Now, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at file permissions in Windows 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 Processes &amp; Services</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/09-windows-processes-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/09-windows-processes-services/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Understanding and Managing Windows Services from How-To Geek Process Explorer Download from Windows Sysinternals Process Library from Uniblue Video Script Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at how Windows interacts with programs. Each program running on an operating system is called a process. Within each process, there can be multiple threads of execution running concurrently. As a system administrator, the most important thing to keep in mind is that each process running on a computer will consume the system&amp;rsquo;s resources, either the available memory or CPU time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 Software Installation</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/10-windows-software-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/10-windows-software-installation/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Installation (Computer Programs) on Wikipedia Here&amp;rsquo;s What Happens when you Install the Top 10 Download.com Apps from How-To Geek Process Monitor from Microsoft Sysinternals InstallWatch Pro from Lo4d.com Video Script One major part of configuring a computer is installing the desired software. However, it is sometimes very difficult to tell exactly what is happening during a software installation, and each time you install software on a system you run the risk of introducing more vulnerabilities and stability issues on the system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 Security &amp; Networking</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/11-windows-security-networking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/11-windows-security-networking/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Adjust Windows 10 Firewall Rules &amp;amp; Settings from Online Tech Tips Configuring Virtual Network Adapter Settings from VMware Using the Virtual Network Editor from VMware Video Script In this last video on Windows 10, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss some important security and networking details needed to finish getting your VMs set up and configured properly.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about security. Whenever you install a new operating system, there are 4 major steps you should always perform before doing just about anything else on the system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Overview &amp; Installation</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/12-ubuntu-overview-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/12-ubuntu-overview-installation/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides VMware/Tools from Ubuntu Ubuntu Features from Ubuntu Ubuntu Desktop Guide from Ubuntu Ubuntu Server Guide from Ubuntu Switching to Ubuntu from Ubuntu Know Thy Ubuntu from Ubuntu Ubuntu 20.04 LTS (Focal Fossa) Download from CS Ubuntu Mirror Linux Distribution Timeline from Wikipedia Desmond Tutu on Ubuntu from YouTube Video Script For the second part of this module, we&amp;rsquo;ll be looking at one other operating system, Ubuntu.
Ubuntu is built using the Linux kernel, which is a completely free and open source operating system kernel developed by Linus Torvalds in 1991.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Terminal</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/13-ubuntu-terminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/13-ubuntu-terminal/</guid>
      <description>Resources Using the Terminal from Ubuntu Advanced Command Line How To from Ubuntu Beginners/Bash Scripting from Ubuntu Environment Variables from Ubuntu Cron How To from Ubuntu An Introduction to the Linux Terminal from DigitalOcean The Ultimate A to Z List of Linux Commands from Fossbytes The Linux Command Line - A Complete Introduction by William E. Schotts Jr. on Amazon LinuxCommand.org Companion Website Linux Tutorial from Ryans Tutorials Video Script One of the most important features of the Linux operating system is the Terminal command line interface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu User Management</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/14-ubuntu-user-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/14-ubuntu-user-management/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides User Accounts from Ubuntu User Management from Ubuntu Server Guide How to Add and Delete Users on Ubuntu 18.04 from DigitalOcean (Works for 20.04) Gnome System Tools Package from Launchpad Install this package to get the GUI to manage Users and Groups The Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Managing Users and Groups in Linux from How-To Geek Linux Users and Groups from Linode Video Script In this video, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to work with users and groups in Ubuntu Linux.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu File Permissions</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/15-ubuntu-file-permissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/15-ubuntu-file-permissions/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides An Introduction to Linux File Permissions from DigitalOcean File Permissions from Ubuntu Enable Open as Administrator on Ubuntu 18.04 from Website for Students chmod on Just Enough Linux Linux Users and Groups on Linode Video Script In this video, we will discuss how file permissions work in Ubuntu Linux. Working with file permissions in Linux is sometimes one of the more challenging aspects of the operating system, as it is very limited compared to Windows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Processes &amp; Services</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/16-ubuntu-processes-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/16-ubuntu-processes-services/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides How to Use ps, kill, and nice to Manage Processes in Linux from DigitalOcean Daemon (Computing) from Wikipedia How to Manage systemd Services on a Linux System from How-To Geek Systemd for Upstart Users from Ubuntu Video Script In this video we&amp;rsquo;ll be looking at managing the processes and services running on an Ubuntu Linux system. First, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at processes. Recall from the earlier video on Windows Processes and Services that a process is a program running in the foreground for the user, while a service is a program running in the background for the operating system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Software Installation</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/17-ubuntu-software-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/17-ubuntu-software-installation/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Install Additional Applications from Ubuntu Use Synaptic for More Advanced Software Management from Ubuntu Apt-Get How To from Ubuntu How Software Installation &amp;amp; Package Managers Work on Linux from How-To Geek Snaps from Snapcraft.io Basic Snap Usage from Ubuntu Tutorials Video Script Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at installing software on Ubuntu Linux. Before we install anything, here is some information about the types of files installed along with a typical application in Ubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Security &amp; Networking</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/18-ubuntu-security-networking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/1-secure-workstations/18-ubuntu-security-networking/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Networking, Web &amp;amp; Email from Ubuntu Networking from Ubuntu Server Guide Internet and Networking from Ubuntu UFW (Uncomplicated Firewall) from Ubuntu GUFW (Graphical Interface for UFW) from Ubuntu Video Script In this last video on Ubuntu, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss some important security and networking details needed to finish getting your VMs set up and configured properly.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about security. Whenever you install a new operating system, there are 4 major steps you should always perform before doing just about anything else on the system.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>