<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Announcements :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/index.html</link><description>Information for Current Students!
Previous Semesters Are Here</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 15:20:01 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fall '25 Week 1</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week01/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week01/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week one announcements video for CIS 527 and CC510 in fall 2025. My name is Russell Feldhausen. I’ll be your instructor for this semester. My contact information is here on the screen. You can also find it on the Canvas homepage, on the syllabus, just about anywhere you look with this class. You can find my contact info. My email is here. My website is here. You can also find me on Teams and Discord as at russfeld. I’m pretty easy to get a hold of. One thing to be aware of, I do work remotely. I live in Kansas City, and so I’m working remotely Tuesdays through Fridays. I am on campus on Mondays. So if you want to see me in person, you can meet with me on Mondays. Usually Monday mornings is when I’m going to be available. And there is a way to schedule that that I’ll talk about here in just a minute. But just be aware of that. The rest of the week, I work remotely, which does mean I’m pretty easy to get a hold of on Teams or Discord or Ed Discussion anytime you have a question.</description></item><item><title>Fall '25 Week 2</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week02/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week02/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week two announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2025. So this week you should be getting started on the first lab. Please bear in mind I do have a megathread on ed discussion for this lab. So if you have any questions or concerns with this lab, I’d really recommend that you post in the ed discussion and also check there, but you can also email to do lab grading. I get a lot of questions about lab grading in this class. The way this works is you’re going to schedule a time slot to meet with either the GTA Josh or myself. You need to meet with us before the lab is due. You can schedule your time slot anytime. So even if you’re not done with the lab right now, you can schedule a time slot for next Wednesday sometime when the lab is due, but you need to have the lab done before that time slot, obviously. So you schedule a time slot. Please check Josh’s calendar first. And then if he doesn’t have any times available that works for you, then schedule with me. Please bear in mind, I am generally very busy on Mondays because I’m on campus and then a little bit on Wednesdays and Thursdays as I have lab meetings and other things going on those days. Tuesdays and Fridays are usually pretty open for me. So anyway, schedule with Josh first, then me using our calendly links, or I also have a booking link that you can use.</description></item><item><title>Fall '25 Week 3</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week03/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week03/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week three announcements video for CIS 527 and CC510 in fall 2025. So this week you should be working on lab one. Lab one is due tomorrow by 7 p.m. So make sure you get that done. Basically all you need to do if you haven’t already is schedule a grading time with either Josh or myself. We will meet with you on Zoom. We will have you share your screen and walk through getting all your lab graded. Remember that every day a lab is late. It is 10% off of the total points in the class or in the project. So this lab is worth 50 points. If you get graded after Wednesday, it’s going to be worth 45 points and it goes down from there. Then next week on Wednesday, the module two quizzes are due. And then the week after that on Wednesday the 24th, Lab 2 is due. Lab two, you don’t have to schedule a grading time for. All the grading for that is done on Canvas. So unless you have questions or want to do an interactive grading, all you have to do for Lab 2 is submit your two puppet manifest files on Canvas and we’ll grade those offline. Also, our first discussion is going to be coming up soon. I’m still waiting to hear back from some of our speakers and I’ll talk about that in just a second.</description></item><item><title>Fall '25 Week 4</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week04/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week04/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week four announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2025. So this week you should be working on lab two. The quizzes for lab two are due this Wednesday, so make sure you get those done soon. The next lab is due on next Wednesday, so you’re going to turn in lab two then. And in two weeks from now, we’re going to have our first discussion. So the questions for that discussion topic are going to be due two weeks from today, actually. So make sure you got that on your calendar.</description></item><item><title>Fall '25 Week 5</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week05/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week05/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week five announcements video for CIS 527 and CC510 in fall 2025. So this week you should be working on lab 2, which is due this Wednesday. We’ll talk about lab 2 in just a second, but remember that’s due tomorrow. Next Tuesday, we’re going to have our first discussion, so make sure you’re planning ahead for that. Next Wednesday is going to be the lab 3 quizzes, and in two weeks, we’re going to have lab 3 due and also our second discussion as well.</description></item><item><title>Fall '25 Week 6</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week06/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week06/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week six announcements video for CIS 527 and CC510 in fall 2025. So, this week today, we’re hosting our first discussion session just shortly after this video gets posted. So, make sure you get the questions in for that. Tomorrow is when the lab three quizzes are going to be due. And then you’ve got until next week to work on lab three. I’m not saying Tuesday, but lab three, I believe, is actually due next Wednesday. But the second discussion will be next Tuesday, so make sure you’re watching out for that.</description></item><item><title>Fall '25 Week 7</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week07/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week07/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week 7 announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2025. So this week you should be working on lab 3. That’s really the only thing going on this week. So lab 3 deadline is this Friday. I did say last week it was due earlier in the week, but I’ve updated the deadline in Canvas to make sure everything matches. So lab 3 will be due this Friday. So make sure you schedule a time to meet with either Josh or I to get your lab 3 graded via Zoom before or on Friday of this week. Then we have a whole week where there’s nothing really due, but you should be working on lab 4. The quizzes for lab four are going to be due Monday, October 20th. And then Tuesday, October 21st, we’re going to have our third discussion prompt, and I’ll talk about that in just a second. And then Friday, 10/24, sorry, I didn’t get that date right. Lab 4 is going to be due. So all these dates are correct on Canvas. So when in doubt, check Canvas. It should always have the correct dates.</description></item><item><title>Fall '25 Week 8</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week08/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week08/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week 8 announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2025. So we don’t really have anything due this week, but next week on Monday are the quizzes for lab 4. Then next Tuesday we’re going to have the third discussion with the current BayoCat sysadmins. And then lab four is going to be due a week from this Friday on the 24th. Then on Tuesday the 28th right before Halloween we’re going to have our second discussion which is Kyle Hudson. But there’s nothing available and nothing due this week. I just want you to get started on lab four and start working on that because it is one of the harder and more time consuming labs for this semester. So make sure you get started on that soon.</description></item><item><title>Fall '25 Week 9</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week09/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week09/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week nine announcements video for CIS527 and CC510 in fall 2025. So this week you should be working on getting lab 4 finished up. Because we had all the outages yesterday, I’ve moved the lab 4 quizzes to tomorrow, which is Wednesday. Today we have our third discussion, which will be today at 2.30 that I’ll talk about briefly. Lab 4 is due this Friday. And then next Tuesday, we’re going to have our second discussion that I will also talk about briefly. So the schedule is a little weird. Hopefully it all makes sense. And all of these dates should also be accurate on Canvas.</description></item><item><title>Fall '25 Week 10</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week10/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week10/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week 10 announcements video for CIS 527 and CC510 in fall 2025. So this week today we’ve got our second discussion. It’s really our third discussion, but it’s discussion two and the announcements. We’ll talk about that. That’s coming up today. Then this Friday your response for discussion three that was last week is going to be due as well as the quizzes for lab five. So make sure you’re watching all those due dates on Canvas.</description></item><item><title>Fall '25 Week 12</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week12/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week12/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week 12 announcements video for CIS 527 and CC510 in fall 2025. So coming up this week, the Lab 6 quizzes are due on Friday. I just posted Lab 6 so you can get started on that. And then Lab 6 itself is going to be due next Friday. That’s the Friday before fall break. So make sure you get that done. And then Lab 7 will be coming up after fall break. But we’ll talk about everything in today’s announcements.</description></item></channel></rss>