<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Announcements :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/</link><description>Information for Current Students!
Previous Semesters Are Here</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:54:26 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fall '24 Week 1</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week01/</guid><description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Hello everyone and welcome to the week one announcements video for CIS 527 and CC fall 10 in fall 2024. So as you probably saw in the introduction video my name is Russ Feldhausen my contact information is here you can find it on Canvas you can find it on the syllabus. I’m really excited to be teaching this class I think this is my eighth time teaching the system administration class.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 2</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week02/</guid><description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the Week 2 Announcements video for CIS 527 and CC510 in Fall 2024. So this week you should be getting ready to have your first lab grading scheduled. So what you need to do to get your labs graded is schedule a time slot to meet with either Josh or myself. Sometime via Zoom before that lab is due. Remember not only do you have to schedule your grading time but the grade time has to happen before the deadline.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 3</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week03/</guid><description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week three announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. So this week lab one is due tomorrow on Wednesday by 7 p .m. so make sure you’re working on getting that completed and don’t forget to schedule a grading time either with myself or with Josh to get that graded. I know my calendar is pretty limited today and tomorrow because of a lot of meetings and I’m on campus tomorrow due to the Labor Day holiday so if you have trouble finding a grading time let us know and we’ll work with you on that.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 4</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week04/</guid><description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week four announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. So this week you should be working on the discussion questions for our first discussion this Wednesday, which will be hosted by Kyle Hutson. I’ll talk about him in just a second. Those questions are due about an hour before the session starts so that I can go through them, but you’re invited to attend live in person so you can see his presentation and ask him questions via Zoom and get your response points there as well.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 5</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week05/</guid><description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week five announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. This week, you should be working on lab two, which is due today. We’ll talk about that momentarily. You also should be working on your response to the first discussion we had last Wednesday with Kyle Hudson. That response is due today, so make sure you get that submitted on Canvas.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 6</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week06/</guid><description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week six announcements video for CIS 527 and CC510 in fall 2024. This week we have our second discussion session hosted on Wednesday, so we’ll talk about that in just a minute. Next Wednesday the response for that discussion is due and the questions for that discussion are due this Wednesday right before we start. And then also next Wednesday lab three is due as well.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 7</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week07/</guid><description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week seven announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. This week you should be working on the response to our second discussion with Seth Galliser. Those responses are due today, so make sure you get those posted. And then this Friday, lab three is due. Hopefully you saw the announcement earlier that I have moved all of the lab deadlines to Friday.</description></item></channel></rss>