<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Announcements :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/</link><description>Information for Current Students!
Previous Semesters Are Here</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:31:32 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fall '23 Week 1</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week01/</guid><description>Ed Discussion This video was recorded before I decided to switch to Ed Discussion instead of using Discord. All discussions of “Discord” can be applied to “Ed Discussion” instead. Sorry for the confusion! - Russ
Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week one announcements for CIS 527 and CC 510. In Fall 2023, my name is Russ Feldhausen. I’ll be your instructor for this semester, my contact information can be found here.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 2</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week02/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week two announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in Fall 2023. I’ll try and post announcements videos like this about every other week in this class. Usually these announcements videos are pretty informal, so you’ll notice I don’t have my background set up or anything, but it’s just a chance for me to talk through some things that are on my mind, things that I would normally announce at the beginning of class if we were meeting in person.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 3</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week03/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the Week Three announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in Fall 2023. So this week lab One is due tomorrow by 07:00 P.m., so make sure you get that done. Remember, for the lab grading, you need to schedule an interactive grading time with either Matt, My, UTA or myself via calendar. Both of our calendars are open. You can schedule a time anytime.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 5</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week05/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week five announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2023. This week we got a lot of stuff going on. We’ve got lab two that’s due on Wednesday, so tomorrow you should be getting done with lab two. There’s also the first discussion will be this Thursday, so the questions for our speaker for the first discussion are also due on Wednesday, so make sure you get those posted.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 8</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week08/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week eight announcements for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2023. So this week you should be wrapping up the second discussion. We had Adam come in and talk about his work on Beocat. So hopefully you’re getting a response put together for that. Also due tomorrow are the quizzes for Lab 4, so hopefully you’re getting those done. And then next week by Wednesday Lab 4 is due, so hopefully you’re able to get started working on that.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 9</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week09/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week09/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week nine announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2023. This week Lab 4 is due tomorrow, so make sure you’re getting Lab 4 all wrapped up. Then you should also be starting on the content for Lab 5, which is some introduction to the cloud. And then a couple weeks from now you’ll have the Lab 5 content that’s actually due, so you should get started on Lab 5 sometime next week.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 12</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/week12/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the Week 12 announcements video for CIS 527 in Fall 2023. As you can tell, I’ve been a little under the weather, so my voice is a little rough. I apologize for that. This week we’ve got a discussion three coming up with Sarah Allen. She’ll be here next Thursday, so please make sure you mark that on your calendar. You’ve got until next Wednesday to come up with a couple of questions.</description></item></channel></rss>