<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fall 2024 :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/index.html</link><description/><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fall '24 Week 1</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week01/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week01/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello everyone and welcome to the week one announcements video for CIS 527 and CC fall 10 in fall 2024. So as you probably saw in the introduction video my name is Russ Feldhausen my contact information is here you can find it on Canvas you can find it on the syllabus. I’m really excited to be teaching this class I think this is my eighth time teaching the system administration class. It’s a really fun class it’s one of the most valuable classes that I get to teach at K -State and I’m really excited to be working through it with you. Every week I’m going to do an announcements video maybe every week maybe every other week it’s generally unscripted it’s me talking through everything that’s in my head so you’re gonna see a much different version of me in these announcements videos versus what you see in the videos for the class.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 2</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week02/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week02/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the Week 2 Announcements video for CIS 527 and CC510 in Fall 2024. So this week you should be getting ready to have your first lab grading scheduled. So what you need to do to get your labs graded is schedule a time slot to meet with either Josh or myself. Sometime via Zoom before that lab is due. Remember not only do you have to schedule your grading time but the grade time has to happen before the deadline. We have some students that are unclear that they just have to schedule the lab grading and then they can get it graded after the deadline. The grading actually has to happen before the deadline.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 3</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week03/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week03/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week three announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. So this week lab one is due tomorrow on Wednesday by 7 p .m. so make sure you’re working on getting that completed and don’t forget to schedule a grading time either with myself or with Josh to get that graded. I know my calendar is pretty limited today and tomorrow because of a lot of meetings and I’m on campus tomorrow due to the Labor Day holiday so if you have trouble finding a grading time let us know and we’ll work with you on that. Generally for the first lab I’m pretty lenient on late penalties as long as you get a grading time scheduled before it’s due and if we have trouble with that let us know. I’m also working with Josh that we may adjust the day of the week that labs are due just to better fit our schedule. It seems like a lot of my meetings tend to have been on the first part of the week so we may move the due dates a little bit just to make more room for that. So make sure you’re getting lab one done. The quizzes for module two are due next week so make sure you’re getting those started and our first discussion prompt is actually on next week on Wednesday September 11th. We’ll talk about that in just a second and then September the 18th is when lab two is due.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 4</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week04/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week04/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week four announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. So this week you should be working on the discussion questions for our first discussion this Wednesday, which will be hosted by Kyle Hutson. I’ll talk about him in just a second. Those questions are due about an hour before the session starts so that I can go through them, but you’re invited to attend live in person so you can see his presentation and ask him questions via Zoom and get your response points there as well. Next week lab two is due on Wednesday so make sure you’re working on lab two to get that done soon and then next Wednesday the response for discussion one is also going to be due.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 5</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week05/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week05/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week five announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. This week, you should be working on lab two, which is due today. We’ll talk about that momentarily. You also should be working on your response to the first discussion we had last Wednesday with Kyle Hudson. That response is due today, so make sure you get that submitted on Canvas. Then you’ll start in on lab three. So the quizzes for lab three are due next week. And then you’ll have the second discussion questions are due next Wednesday. And then in two weeks, you’ll be turning in lab three and your second discussion.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 6</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week06/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week06/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week six announcements video for CIS 527 and CC510 in fall 2024. This week we have our second discussion session hosted on Wednesday, so we’ll talk about that in just a minute. Next Wednesday the response for that discussion is due and the questions for that discussion are due this Wednesday right before we start. And then also next Wednesday lab three is due as well. So for lab three, which you should be working on this week is adding some core network services to our Ubuntu VMs. You’re going to set static IP addresses. You’re going to install a DNS server and a DHCP server. You’re also going to install SNMP so that you can view some of your network statistics across the network. You’ll also install Wireshark and use that to capture some packets. All of this is really useful stuff to understand how networking services work.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 7</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week07/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week07/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week seven announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. This week you should be working on the response to our second discussion with Seth Galliser. Those responses are due today, so make sure you get those posted. And then this Friday, lab three is due. Hopefully you saw the announcement earlier that I have moved all of the lab deadlines to Friday. That seems to work better for Josh and I and our schedule. We have a lot more time for grading on Wednesday, Thursday, Friday. Please bear in mind, you can go ahead and schedule your grading time right now as long as you know you’re going to have your lab done before that deadline. So if you want to reserve your time on Friday, go ahead and get it scheduled and we will take care of that. But just bear in mind that labs are now due on Fridays and then for the times when that conflicts I’ve moved things around. So just check the deadlines in Canvas because those are the accurate timelines for all of this.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 8</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week08/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week08/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week 8 announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. So coming up we’re working on lab 4 so by next Monday you should have the quizzes done for lab 4 and then by next Friday you’ll be turning in lab 4 itself. This really this couple of weeks this is probably the hardest part of this class I know a lot of students struggle with getting lab 4 up and running not necessarily because it’s difficult but because there’s a lot of bits and pieces to deal with and there’s a lot of dependencies that you have to work around as well. So those are all things to keep in mind.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 9</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week09/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week09/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week nine announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. I’m coming to you this week from my office on campus because I’m on the road a little bit. Hopefully the video quality is not too bad and you can get everything that I need to get across in these announcements. So for this week you should be working on lab four. Lab four is due this Friday so make sure that you’re getting that done and have your grading time scheduled. Right now I have a lot of availability on Friday and I believe Josh should also have availability toward the end of the week so hopefully you can get your grading time scheduled. If you’re having any questions or issues with the lab let us know and we’ll definitely work with you on that and then next week you’ll transition over and start working on lab five.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 10</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week10/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week10/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week 10 announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. So this week you should get started on working on lab five, which is our first lab completely done in the cloud and DigitalOcean. That lab is going to be due next Friday by 5 p .m. So make sure you get that done and are scheduled to get that graded. We also have our next discussion session coming up, not this Wednesday, but next Wednesday, October 30th.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 11</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week11/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week11/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week 11 announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. This week, you’re working on lab 5, lab 5 is due on Friday. As before, you’ll need to schedule a grading time with either Josh or I to get your lab graded. Lab 5 is pretty straightforward to grade, we’re just going to check some settings on your digital ocean droplets, and then we’re going to make sure that you’ve set up a domain name and have HTTPS working, the Apache sites working, and the Docker sites working. It usually only takes a few minutes to grade if everything’s working correctly. So hopefully you get everything done. Lab 5 is usually a little bit of a downward curve on the difficulty in this class, so hopefully it goes well. Also, don’t forget, our third discussion session is coming up tomorrow, Wednesday this week at 2:30.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 12</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week12/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week12/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week 12 announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. So you should be starting on lab six this week. Lab six is going to be due next week on Friday. We’re also going to have our fourth discussion session next week on Wednesday. So our next discussion speaker is Sarah Allen. Sarah Allen is a computer support person for McCon Gordon construction. Sarah was a student in this class a few years ago and now works in industry as a frontline support tech. She has a lot of good experience and stories to tell from working in that industry. So she’s going to come in and be our guest speaker this Wednesday, November 13th. So a week from this Wednesday at 2 30 p .m. So make sure you put that on your calendar. The questions post is already up so you can get questions asked for Sarah. I’ve also linked her LinkedIn so you can learn a little bit more about her background and what she does.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 13</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week13/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week13/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week 13 announcements video for CIS 527 and CC510 in fall 2024. This week you should be working on lab six, which is due on Friday. So make sure you get your grading time scheduled sometime this week to get that turned in. We’re also going to have our fourth discussion session this Wednesday. So make sure you get those questions posted before two o’clock that day. And then you’ll be able to meet with our speaker and ask questions when she speaks at 2.30.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 14</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week14/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week14/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week 14 announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. So remaining in this class is just a few things. The discussion for response is due tomorrow, so make sure you get that turned in. Your project proposal is due this Friday, so that’s just your quick proposal for your final project. It should be about a paragraph or so. And then the rest of the class, Lab 7 and the final project are both due by the end of finals week. And then of course you’ll also get some TVALs from me as well.</description></item><item><title>Fall '24 Week 15</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week15/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2024/week15/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week 15 announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2024. So all that’s really remaining in this class is lab 7 and the final project both of which are due on the Friday of finals week so you’ve got a little bit over a week and a half to work on those. We’ll also have teaching evaluations at the end of the semester so let’s talk about all of that.</description></item></channel></rss>