<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Application Servers :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/</link><description>Putting your resources to work.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 17:29:55 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/01-introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/01-introduction/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Transcript Welcome to Module 6! In this module, we’ll discuss the various types of servers that you may come across in a large organization. This could include file servers, web servers, application servers, database servers, and more!
In the lab assignment, you’ll set up a file server on both Windows and Ubuntu, and deal with automatically providing access to those resources for your users. You’ll also configure the IIS and Apache web servers, and learn about installing an application on each.</description></item><item><title>Application Servers Overview</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/02-application-servers-overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/02-application-servers-overview/</guid><description>Resources Slides 10 Tips for Successfully Implementing Enterprise Software from Liquid State An Analyst’s Guide to Evaluating Enterprise Software from Automation World 18 Enterprise Software Selection Risks and How to Avoid Them from CIO.com Video Transcript This module is all about application servers. So, before we begin talking about them in-depth, we should first discuss what an application server actually is.
In this class, I’ll be referring to an application server as any server that runs an enterprise application.</description></item><item><title>Assignment</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/03-assignment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/03-assignment/</guid><description>Lab 6 - Application Servers Instructions Create two cloud systems and four virtual machines meeting the specifications given below. The best way to accomplish this is to treat this assignment like a checklist and check things off as you complete them.
If you have any questions about these items or are unsure what they mean, please contact the instructor. Remember that part of being a system administrator (and a software developer in general) is working within vague specifications to provide what your client is requesting, so eliciting additional information is a very necessary skill.</description></item><item><title>File Servers Overview</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/04-file-servers-overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/04-file-servers-overview/</guid><description>Resources Slides Standard RAID Levels on Wikipedia Nested RAID Levelson Wikipedia Parity from Crystal Clear Mathematics What are the Different Types of Storage: Block, Object and File? on Ubuntu Blog NAS vs. SAN vs. DAS: Which is Right for You? from Seagate Blog Getting Started with Storage: Understanding SAN vs NAS vs DAS from Vanilla Video Video Transcript The first type of application server we will cover in this module is the file server.</description></item><item><title>Windows File Server</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/05-windows-file-server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/05-windows-file-server/</guid><description>Resources Windows Group Policy How to Share Files and Folders in Windows Server 2016 from Tactig How to Map Network Drives with Group Policy (Complete Guide) by Robert Allen on Active Directory Pro How to: Mapping Network Drives/Folders via Group Policy on Spiceworks Community Video Transcript In this video, I’ll briefly walk you through the steps of setting up a file server in Windows Server 2016, as well as how to access those resources from a Windows 10 client on the same network.</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu File Server</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/06-ubuntu-file-server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/06-ubuntu-file-server/</guid><description>Resources File Server from Ubuntu Documentation Samba Server Guide from Ubuntu Community Help Wiki How to Set Up a Samba Share for a Small Organization on Ubuntu 16.04 from DigitalOcean (works for 20.04) Access User’s Home Folders via Samba on Ubuntu 17.04 from Website for Students (works for 20.04) Mount Windows Shares Permanently from Ubuntu Wiki How Do I Access Windows Shares from Bash on Ask Ubuntu Forums Use of pam-mount to Mount Home from Server on Ubuntu Forums Video Transcript In this video, I’ll walk you through the steps to set up a file server on Ubuntu using Samba.</description></item><item><title>Web Servers Overview</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/07-web-servers-overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/07-web-servers-overview/</guid><description>Resources Slides Web Server on Wikipedia LAMP (Software Bundle) from Wikipedia Nginx from Wikipedia Web Server Survey from Netcraft Video Transcript Another common type of application server in many enterprises is a web server. A web server is the software that is used to make websites available on the World Wide Web. So, it is responsible for listening and responding to HTTP requests. The software is typically designed so it can handle many simultaneous connections, and even serve multiple websites as we saw in Lab 5.</description></item><item><title>Database Servers</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/08-database-servers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/08-database-servers/</guid><description>Resources Slides 5 Tips for Managing Database Servers in Production from Cloud 66 10 Easy Tips for Better SQL Server Performance from ITPro Today What Kind of Disks Should You Use with Microsoft SQL Server 2016? from Heroix Blog Database Encryption on Wikipedia Encrypting Data at Rest on Servers: What Does it Get You? from HLN Consulting Video Transcript One of the other most commonly used application servers in an enterprise is a database server.</description></item><item><title>Windows Web Server</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/09-windows-web-server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/09-windows-web-server/</guid><description>Note The first part of this video references ASP.NET 4.6, which has been replaced by ASP.NET 4.7 in Windows Server 2019.
Resources URL Rewrite from Microsoft Add A Website to Windows Server 2016 using Host Headers from Ionos by 1&amp;1 How to add DNS Forward Lookup Zone in Windows Server 2019 from Computingforgeeks How to add DNS A/PTR Record in Windows Server 2019 from Computingforgeeks How to Create a Self Signed Certificate in IIS from AboutSSL Microsoft Server 2016 - IIS 10 &amp; 10.</description></item><item><title>Windows Web Application</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/10-windows-web-application/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/10-windows-web-application/</guid><description>Note Unfortunately the software used in this example is no longer available publicly, so you won’t be able to follow along directly with the video.
Resources SQL Server 2017 Express Edition from Microsoft Video Transcript In this video, I’ll go through some of the basic steps to install a .NET web application on your server. For this example, I’ll be using a trial version of the JitBit .NET Forum software, as it is a good representative example of what it takes to deploy an existing .</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu Web Server</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/11-ubuntu-web-server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/11-ubuntu-web-server/</guid><description>Note It appears that MySQL will now be installed with TLS enabled on Ubuntu 20.04, so you may not have to do that step. –Russ
Resources Install MySQL on Ubuntu 20.04 LTS Linux from LinuxConfig.org How To Install and Secure phpMyAdmin on Ubuntu 18.04 from DigitalOcean (works for 20.04) How To Install the Apache Web Server on Ubuntu 20.04 from DigitalOcean How To Secure Apache with Let’s Encrypt on Ubuntu 20.</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu Web Application</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/12-ubuntu-web-application/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/6-application-servers/12-ubuntu-web-application/</guid><description>Resources phpBB Installation from phpBB How To Set Up A Remote Database to Optimize Site Performance with MySQL on Ubuntu 20.04 from DigitalOcean (works for 24.04) Video Transcript In this video, I’ll discuss the steps you’ll need to follow in order to install a new web application that uses PHP and MySQL on the environment we created in the last video. As with the previous videos discussing web applications on a Windows server, you’ll have to adapt these steps to match the application you are installing and the particular configuration of your environment.</description></item></channel></rss>