




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fall 2021 on CIS 527 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fall 2021 on CIS 527 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 1</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week01/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week01/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week one Announcements video for CC 510. In Fall 2022, I&amp;rsquo;m Russ Feldhausen. I&amp;rsquo;ll be your instructor for this semester, my contact information is here. It&amp;rsquo;s also on the syllabus, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to get ahold of me. For this course, email is preferred. So please email me at russfeld@ksu.edu. But you can also chat with me on Discord, I&amp;rsquo;m @russfeld. Most of you have already posted You&amp;rsquo;re welcome there, which is great.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 3</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week03/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week03/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week three announcements video for CC 510 in Fall 2022. Hopefully today you&amp;rsquo;re wrapping up lab one, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, make sure you schedule the time to meet with me to get that graded. That&amp;rsquo;s due tonight by 7pm. And then we&amp;rsquo;ll start launching into module two. The week two quizzes are due next Monday. And then lab two is due the week after that along with the second week&amp;rsquo;s discussion, which is actually the first discussion for this semester.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 5</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week05/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week05/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week five announcements video for CC 510 In Fall 2022, this week you should be wrapping up lab two, which was technically due yesterday. So hopefully you got that submitted discussion. One was also due yesterday. So make sure that you&amp;rsquo;ve watched that video and responded to those questions, you can also ask a few more questions that you&amp;rsquo;d like me to send on the Seth and I will try and get some responses for that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 7</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week07/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week07/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week seven Announcements video for CC 510 In Fall 2022, this week, lab three is due. So hopefully you&amp;rsquo;re getting that done and turned in and have a scheduled time to meet with me for grading. If not, make sure you get that done ASAP. So you can keep moving ahead in this class, you also should have been completing discussion to which is due on Canvas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 9</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week09/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week09/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week nine announcements for CC 510 in fall 2022. So this week, lab four is due, I believe most of you scheduled time either yesterday or today to get lab four graded. So good job on that. Hopefully that&amp;rsquo;s all working well. And then you&amp;rsquo;ll also start working on lab five content this week. Next week, lab five, you&amp;rsquo;re going to be working on it, it&amp;rsquo;ll be due the following Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 11</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week11/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week11/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week 11 Announcements video for CC 510 In Fall 2022, this week, you should be wrapping up lab five, which was due yesterday. So if you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, make sure you schedule a time to get lab five graded. You&amp;rsquo;re also should be looking at the third discussion in this class, which is due next week. And then you&amp;rsquo;ll be starting on lab six with quizzes due next week and lab six itself being due the following week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 13</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week13/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week13/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week 13 announcements for CC 510 in fall 2022. So this is a list of everything that&amp;rsquo;s remaining do in this class. For the rest of the semester, we&amp;rsquo;ve got lab six that&amp;rsquo;s due today, you&amp;rsquo;ve got a discussion that&amp;rsquo;s due after Thanksgiving, your final project proposal is due after Thanksgiving. And then we have lab seven, discussion, five. And the final project I&amp;rsquo;ll do right around finals week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 14</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week14/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/week14/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week 14 Announcements video for CC 510 in fall 2022, so remaining in this class, there is a discussion that was due yesterday. Hopefully you got that done and submitted along with the questions for our presenter. The final project proposal is due this Friday, so make sure you&amp;rsquo;re working on that final project proposal. It&amp;rsquo;s just a short one page that explains your project and kind of tells me you&amp;rsquo;re on the right track and can work on it for the last two weeks of the class.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>