<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fall '23 Week 8 :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week08/index.html</link><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week eight announcements for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2023. So this week you should be wrapping up the second discussion. We had Adam come in and talk about his work on Beocat. So hopefully you’re getting a response put together for that. Also due tomorrow are the quizzes for Lab 4, so hopefully you’re getting those done. And then next week by Wednesday Lab 4 is due, so hopefully you’re able to get started working on that. So some quick hints real quick about success in this course because I get asked this question every once in a while. Things that you can do to be really successful in this course is to read the lab assignments very, very carefully. There’s a lot of information in there, but there’s also a lot of hints in there about ways to do things or pitfalls we’ve run into. Those red and green and blue boxes are things that I’ve added in over the years that I think are very helpful. The linked documentation is also very helpful. A lot of times the work you’re trying to do in the lab can be accomplished by following that first or second documentation link and following the steps there. I try and post them in the order of relevance, so most likely start with the first one. It will probably answer most of your questions. But if you do get stuck in this class, if you’re not making forward progress after about an hour or if something breaks and you can’t figure it out, that is a great time to take a stop and ask questions. There’s a lot of things both Matt and I know how to help you with that it’s just impossible for us to explain in the class. For example, things like how to check your system log, how to restart services and look for bugs and how to look at these config files and see what’s going on. Especially with Lab 4, you have to be diagnosing network issues and also looking at domain issues and trying to get your certificates to work. There’s a lot of intricacy in Lab 4. If you get stuck, don’t spin your wheels. Please come talk to us. We’ve got a lot of time. Matt will be having office hours on Thursday during the one o ‘clock time. I should be there as well for a little while. Hopefully, you can use some of these tips to be successful in this course.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week08/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/></channel></rss>