<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fall 2023 :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/index.html</link><description/><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fall '23 Week 1</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week01/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week01/index.html</guid><description>Ed Discussion This video was recorded before I decided to switch to Ed Discussion instead of using Discord. All discussions of “Discord” can be applied to “Ed Discussion” instead. Sorry for the confusion! - Russ
Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week one announcements for CIS 527 and CC 510. In Fall 2023, my name is Russ Feldhausen. I’ll be your instructor for this semester, my contact information can be found here. It’s also on the syllabus. It’s also on the cannabis page. Feel free to reach out to me if you have any questions or concerns at all in this class. I also have one teaching assistant this semester, Matt Schwartz, Matt is going to be working with me to help you if you have any questions on the labs, he’s also going to be helping me with doing some of the grading Matt did this class last year, I believe. So he’s pretty familiar with a lot of the content. And he’s going to be working right alongside you to check all the labs for me. So if you have any questions, feel free to reach out to either of us, we’re happy to help. In this course, just like a lot of courses, it’s built with gated modules on canvas. There’s one module due every other week in this class, so please check the due dates very carefully. Each module includes a lab assignment, that lab assignment requires a live grading portion, which means you’ll work with either Matt or myself via zoom, so that we can grade your work, it means that this is a very labor intensive class. So please be aware of that. We’re also going to have some discussions throughout the semester. So you’ll either have a recorded video to watch, or I’ll bring in a guest speaker and you’ll have the opportunity to join a live zoom and speak with one of our guest speakers. And then finally, at the end of the semester, we’ll have a final project.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 2</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week02/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week02/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week two announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in Fall 2023. I’ll try and post announcements videos like this about every other week in this class. Usually these announcements videos are pretty informal, so you’ll notice I don’t have my background set up or anything, but it’s just a chance for me to talk through some things that are on my mind, things that I would normally announce at the beginning of class if we were meeting in person. But instead, I think it’s much easier to do these quick videos is.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 3</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week03/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week03/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the Week Three announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in Fall 2023. So this week lab One is due tomorrow by 07:00 P.m., so make sure you get that done. Remember, for the lab grading, you need to schedule an interactive grading time with either Matt, My, UTA or myself via calendar. Both of our calendars are open. You can schedule a time anytime. However, please bear in mind that most of the time you have to schedule a meeting at least 2 hours in advance. So don’t wait until tomorrow afternoon because we may be all full. And then you’ll have to schedule for Thursday so make sure you get that scheduled ASAP. The lab is due before 07:00 P.m. Just to account for some late stuff in case people schedule for after work. Also, don’t forget that the Week Two quizzes are due next week. So on September 11 on Monday, make sure you get those done. And then lab Two is going to be due on September 20. We’re also shooting on having a discussion around that same time as well and I’ll briefly talk about that.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 5</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week05/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week05/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week five announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2023. This week we got a lot of stuff going on. We’ve got lab two that’s due on Wednesday, so tomorrow you should be getting done with lab two. There’s also the first discussion will be this Thursday, so the questions for our speaker for the first discussion are also due on Wednesday, so make sure you get those posted. Then we go into next Monday. You’ve got lab three quizzes due or due next Monday. Next Wednesday the discussion one responses due if you’re not able to attend a live discussion and then two weeks from now lab three is due and the second discussion questions will be due because our second speaker will be that week. So there’s stuff due every week, sometimes on Monday and Wednesday, so make sure you’re watching your calendar. Hopefully things go really smoothly, but it’s a really good time to keep keeping on your Canvas calendar to make sure you don’t miss anything that is due coming up.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 8</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week08/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week08/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week eight announcements for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2023. So this week you should be wrapping up the second discussion. We had Adam come in and talk about his work on Beocat. So hopefully you’re getting a response put together for that. Also due tomorrow are the quizzes for Lab 4, so hopefully you’re getting those done. And then next week by Wednesday Lab 4 is due, so hopefully you’re able to get started working on that. So some quick hints real quick about success in this course because I get asked this question every once in a while. Things that you can do to be really successful in this course is to read the lab assignments very, very carefully. There’s a lot of information in there, but there’s also a lot of hints in there about ways to do things or pitfalls we’ve run into. Those red and green and blue boxes are things that I’ve added in over the years that I think are very helpful. The linked documentation is also very helpful. A lot of times the work you’re trying to do in the lab can be accomplished by following that first or second documentation link and following the steps there. I try and post them in the order of relevance, so most likely start with the first one. It will probably answer most of your questions. But if you do get stuck in this class, if you’re not making forward progress after about an hour or if something breaks and you can’t figure it out, that is a great time to take a stop and ask questions. There’s a lot of things both Matt and I know how to help you with that it’s just impossible for us to explain in the class. For example, things like how to check your system log, how to restart services and look for bugs and how to look at these config files and see what’s going on. Especially with Lab 4, you have to be diagnosing network issues and also looking at domain issues and trying to get your certificates to work. There’s a lot of intricacy in Lab 4. If you get stuck, don’t spin your wheels. Please come talk to us. We’ve got a lot of time. Matt will be having office hours on Thursday during the one o ‘clock time. I should be there as well for a little while. Hopefully, you can use some of these tips to be successful in this course.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 9</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week09/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week09/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week nine announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2023. This week Lab 4 is due tomorrow, so make sure you’re getting Lab 4 all wrapped up. Then you should also be starting on the content for Lab 5, which is some introduction to the cloud. And then a couple weeks from now you’ll have the Lab 5 content that’s actually due, so you should get started on Lab 5 sometime next week. So for grading on Lab 4, basically we want to see a few simple things. We want to see your Windows Server up and running with an Active Directory installed and a static IP address. We want to see that you’ve created a user and group and Active Directory, and we want to show that you’ve connected a Windows client to that Active Directory. Then we’ll shift over to Linux. We want to see that you’ve installed Open LDAP and you’ve created a user and group using LDAP Account Manager. I posted an announcements video yesterday with a video showing you how to install LDAP Account Manager, so hopefully that helps. I apologize for the bad audio quality on that video. It was recorded on my laptop, which doesn’t have a good microphone. I will re -record a more professional version of that video in the future. And then we want to see you have an Ubuntu client that logs into LDAP using the LDAP client. We also want to have an Ubuntu that logs into your Active Directory. Those could be two different VMs, two different snapshots of the same VM. It’s up to you how you want to handle that. But that’s really all we want to see with Lab 4. If everything’s working, it takes very little time to show us that it’s working. If you have trouble, feel free to work with Matt or I, and we’d be happy to help you debug it. We’re slowly getting better with debugging problems with Lab 4.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 12</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week12/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week12/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the Week 12 announcements video for CIS 527 in Fall 2023. As you can tell, I’ve been a little under the weather, so my voice is a little rough. I apologize for that. This week we’ve got a discussion three coming up with Sarah Allen. She’ll be here next Thursday, so please make sure you mark that on your calendar. You’ve got until next Wednesday to come up with a couple of questions. You’d like to ask Sarah based on her experience working as a system administrator for McCown -Gordon. After her presentation, you’ll have a couple of weeks to work on a response if you weren’t able to attend in person. Lab 6, the quizzes are due this week and then Lab 6 is due next week. Lab 6 is kind of one of the big wrap -up labs where we talk about big things like file servers, mapping drives to those file servers, creating application servers, and building some working web applications. It’s like three or four different things that we all do in different ways, but this uses all your VMs and your digital ocean droplets as well.</description></item></channel></rss>