<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directory Services :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/index.html</link><description>Consistent usernames across devices.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:42:37 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/01-introduction/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/01-introduction/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Transcript Welcome to Module 4! In this module, we’ll discuss how to use directory services to provide consistent user accounts and permissions across a number of systems. Specifically, we’ll look at the Active Directory Domain Services for Windows, and the OpenLDAP implementation of the Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP) for Ubuntu Linux.</description></item><item><title>Directory Services Overview</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/02-directory-services-overview/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/02-directory-services-overview/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Active Directory on Wikipedia Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP) on Wikipedia Samba (Software) on Wikipedia NetIQ eDirectory on Wikipedia (previously Novell Directory Services) Overview of Novell Directory Services from Novell Kerberos (Protocol) on Wikipedia RFC 1510 - Kerberos from IETF Directories, Directory Services, and LDAP from Apache Understanding Workgroups and Domains from eTutorials.org Video Transcript This video presents a brief overview of directory services and related concepts. This information is very helpful in understanding the larger role that many of these services play in modern computer networks.</description></item><item><title>Assignment</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/03-assignment/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/03-assignment/index.html</guid><description>Lab 4 - Directory Services Instructions Create four virtual machines meeting the specifications given below. The best way to accomplish this is to treat this assignment like a checklist and check things off as you complete them.
If you have any questions about these items or are unsure what they mean, please contact the instructor. Remember that part of being a system administrator (and a software developer in general) is working within vague specifications to provide what your client is requesting, so eliciting additional information is a very necessary skill.</description></item><item><title>Windows Active Directory Installation</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/04-windows-active-directory-installation/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/04-windows-active-directory-installation/index.html</guid><description>Note This video uses Windows Server 2016, but the process should be functionally identical in Windows Server 2019. Also make sure you refer to the Lab 4 assignment for the correct root domain name. –Russ
Resources Step-By-Step: Setting Up Active Directory in Windows Server 2016 from Microsoft Add User Accounts on Active Directory from Server-World AD DS Installation and Removal Wizard Page Descriptions from Microsoft NetBIOS on Wikipedia Video Transcript In this video, I’ll go through some of the process of configuring a Windows Server 2016 VM to act as an Active Directory Domain Controller. The goal of this video isn’t to show you all the steps of the process, but provide commentary on some of the more confusing steps you’ll perform.</description></item><item><title>Windows Client Configuration</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/05-windows-client-configuration/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/05-windows-client-configuration/index.html</guid><description>Resources Join a Computer to a Domain from Microsoft Support Video Transcript Once you have completely set up your Active Directory Domain, you can begin to add Windows clients to the domain. This video will walk through some of that process, and I’ll discuss a few of the steps as we go.</description></item><item><title>Windows Group Policy</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/06-windows-group-policy/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/06-windows-group-policy/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Group Policy on Wikipedia Group Policy Processing and Precedence from Microsoft Docs Group Policy Fundamentals in Active Directory by Troy Thompson in Redmond Magazine What is Group Policy in Windows from How-To Geek The 10 Windows Group Policy Settings you Need to Get Right from CSO Online In the Trenches: Eight Tips-n-Tricks for Microsoft Windows Group Policy by Mark Mizrahi on Global Knowledge Top 10 Most Important Group Policy Settings for Preventing Security Breaches by Abhishek Rai on Lepide Blog Group Policy Best Practices by Robert Allen on Active Directory Pro Optimizing Group Policy Performance by Darren Mar-Elia on Microsoft TechNet Video Transcript One of the major features of Microsoft’s Active Directory is the ability to use Group Policy Objects, or GPOs, to enforce specific security settings on any Windows client added to the domain. For large enterprises, this is a major tool in their arsenal to ensure that Windows PCs are properly configured and secured in their organization.</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu LDAP Installation</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/07-ubuntu-ldap-installation/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/07-ubuntu-ldap-installation/index.html</guid><description>Note PHPLDAPAdmin no longer works on Ubuntu 24.04 since it has several incompatibility issues with PHP 8+. The assignment has been updated to use the new LDAP Account Manager (LAM) software instead. You may ignore the part of this video showing how to configure PHPLDAPAdmin and instead refer to the guide linked from the assignment page to configure LAM.</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu Client Configuration</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/08-ubuntu-client-configuration/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/08-ubuntu-client-configuration/index.html</guid><description>Note See the transcript below for an updated version of the ldapwhoami command.
Resources SSSD and LDAP on Ubuntu Server Guide Video Transcript Once we’ve set up and configured our OpenLDAP server on Linux, we can configure another VM to act as an LDAP client and use that server for authentication. Thankfully, now that Ubuntu 20.04 uses SSSD, this process is pretty simple.</description></item><item><title>Linux Client on Windows Domain</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/09-linux-client-on-windows-domain/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/09-linux-client-on-windows-domain/index.html</guid><description>Resources SSSD and Active Directory from Ubuntu Join in Active Directory Domain from Server-World (works for 24.04) How to Join Ubuntu 18.04 / Debian 10 To Active Directory (AD) Domain from Computingforgeeks (works for 24.04) Video Transcript In the following two videos, we’ll look at how to enable interoperability between our Windows- and Linux-based systems. In many organizations today, you’ll have a mix of many different operating systems, so it is very helpful to understand how to integrate them together in a single directory service.</description></item><item><title>Windows Client on Linux Domain</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/10-windows-client-on-linux-domain/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/10-windows-client-on-linux-domain/index.html</guid><description>Note This portion is no longer part of the Lab 4 assignment, but I left it here because it is interesting to know that it can be done. –Russ
Resources How to Configure Ubuntu Linux Server as a Domain Controller with Samba-tool by Jack Wallen on TechRepublic Samba Not Starting on Ubuntu Server 16.10 from StackExchange How to Disable Systemd-resolved in Ubuntu from AskUbuntu Video Transcript In this video, I’ll show you how to set up an Ubuntu VM to act as a Windows Active Directory Domain Controller using Samba. Unfortunately, at this time it is not straightforward at all to use OpenLDAP as the server, hence the decision to use Samba instead. This is a much more complicated process than adding Ubuntu as a client to an existing Active Directory Domain, but I feel that it is important to see that it is indeed possible. This is helpful if your organization is primarily Linux-based, but you wish to include a few Windows clients on the network as well.</description></item><item><title>AD and NETBIOS Names</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/11-adds-netbios/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/11-adds-netbios/index.html</guid><description>It appears that I have managed to confuse lots of people with the Windows AD portion of this lab. That’s not my intent, and any confusion is totally my fault here. This is mostly due to the fact that I reused an older video showing how to set up an Active Directory server and not clearly describing how things should be changed. I’ll do my best to clarify what you need to know and how you can adapt any existing setup you may have so that it works.</description></item><item><title>Lab 4 Networking Diagrams</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/12-lab4-networking/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/12-lab4-networking/index.html</guid><description>Here are some helpful networking diagrams to better explain the desired state before and after the end of Lab 4. In all of these diagrams, I am using a sample network with the IP address 192.168.40.0. You will have to adapt the IPs to match your network configuration. In addition, each network address will need to be updated with your unique eID as directed in the lab assignment.</description></item><item><title>Creating Azure VMs</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/13-azurevms/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/13-azurevms/index.html</guid><description>Warning I failed to mention in the video that you cannot use the Remote Desktop Connection to access Azure VMs while on the K-State Campus Network. K-State has blocked all outgoing RDP connections. So, you must either work from a network location that is not on campus, or use a VPN to access a network outside of K-State.
Edited Transcript In this video, I’m going to go through the process of setting up a virtual machine in Azure for the system administration class. This is really useful for students that either have a newer MacBook that aren’t able to virtualize Windows Server yet, but it’s also useful for anybody that either has a lower powered system that wants to virtualize things in the cloud, or if you just want to get more experience working with Azure as a cloud service provider. So to get access to Azure, we’re going to start at the CS support page, which is support .cs .ksu .edu. And in here under the FAQs, there’s a link right here that says, I need some software by Microsoft. If you click that link, that will take you to this page. And right here, it has this link for the Microsoft Azure DevTools for Teaching. This link tends to change over time, but this page will always be kept up to date with the correct link. So I’m going to click that link, and it’s going to take me to a page where I can sign in. This used to use a different account system. Now it actually uses your K -State single sign -on account. So I’m going to go ahead and sign in to Azure using that account. It’s going to take me to my organization sign -in page. So I’ll sign in through K -State. It may need to do two factor if it needs to. And then it will pop in and take me to this page.</description></item></channel></rss>