<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Summer 2021 Syllabus :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/05-syllabus/old/summer2021/index.html</link><description>CIS 527 - Enterprise Systems Administration CC 510 - Computer Systems Administration This syllabus covers both courses. They are taught using the same content.
Instructor Contact Information Instructor: Russell Feldhausen (russfeld AT ksu DOT edu)
I use he/him pronouns. Feel free to share your own pronouns with me, and I’ll do my best to use them! Office: DUE 2184, but I mostly work remotely from Kansas City, MO Phone: (785) 292-3121 (Call/Text) Website: https://russfeld.me Virtual Office Hours: By appointment via Zoom. Schedule a meeting at https://calendly.com/russfeld Preferred Methods of Communication: Email: Email is the official method of communication for this course. Any emails sent to the instructor regarding this course should be answered within one class day. Discord: There is a #cis-527_cc-510 channel on the K-State CS Discord Server for this course. Students are encouraged to post questions there and use that space for discussion. The instructor will also participate in that channel, but no guarantees of response time are given. Phone/Text: Emergencies only! We will do our best to respond as quickly as we can. Prerequisites CIS 527: CIS 300. Students may enroll in CIS courses only if they have earned a grade of C or better for each prerequisite to those courses. CC 510: CC 310 or CIS 300. Course Structure This course is being taught 100% online and mostly asynchronous. There may be some bumps in the road. Students will work at their own pace through several modules, with due dates for completion of each module given. Material will be provided in the form of recorded videos, links to online resources, and discussion prompts. Each module will include a hands-on lab assignment, which will be graded interactively by the instructor or GTAs. Assignments may also include written portions or presentations, which will be submitted online.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/0-introduction/05-syllabus/old/summer2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/></channel></rss>