<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fall '23 Week 9 :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week09/index.html</link><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week nine announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2023. This week Lab 4 is due tomorrow, so make sure you’re getting Lab 4 all wrapped up. Then you should also be starting on the content for Lab 5, which is some introduction to the cloud. And then a couple weeks from now you’ll have the Lab 5 content that’s actually due, so you should get started on Lab 5 sometime next week. So for grading on Lab 4, basically we want to see a few simple things. We want to see your Windows Server up and running with an Active Directory installed and a static IP address. We want to see that you’ve created a user and group and Active Directory, and we want to show that you’ve connected a Windows client to that Active Directory. Then we’ll shift over to Linux. We want to see that you’ve installed Open LDAP and you’ve created a user and group using LDAP Account Manager. I posted an announcements video yesterday with a video showing you how to install LDAP Account Manager, so hopefully that helps. I apologize for the bad audio quality on that video. It was recorded on my laptop, which doesn’t have a good microphone. I will re -record a more professional version of that video in the future. And then we want to see you have an Ubuntu client that logs into LDAP using the LDAP client. We also want to have an Ubuntu that logs into your Active Directory. Those could be two different VMs, two different snapshots of the same VM. It’s up to you how you want to handle that. But that’s really all we want to see with Lab 4. If everything’s working, it takes very little time to show us that it’s working. If you have trouble, feel free to work with Matt or I, and we’d be happy to help you debug it. We’re slowly getting better with debugging problems with Lab 4.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week09/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/></channel></rss>