<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Creating Azure VMs :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/13-azurevms/index.html</link><description>Warning I failed to mention in the video that you cannot use the Remote Desktop Connection to access Azure VMs while on the K-State Campus Network. K-State has blocked all outgoing RDP connections. So, you must either work from a network location that is not on campus, or use a VPN to access a network outside of K-State.
Edited Transcript In this video, I’m going to go through the process of setting up a virtual machine in Azure for the system administration class. This is really useful for students that either have a newer MacBook that aren’t able to virtualize Windows Server yet, but it’s also useful for anybody that either has a lower powered system that wants to virtualize things in the cloud, or if you just want to get more experience working with Azure as a cloud service provider. So to get access to Azure, we’re going to start at the CS support page, which is support .cs .ksu .edu. And in here under the FAQs, there’s a link right here that says, I need some software by Microsoft. If you click that link, that will take you to this page. And right here, it has this link for the Microsoft Azure DevTools for Teaching. This link tends to change over time, but this page will always be kept up to date with the correct link. So I’m going to click that link, and it’s going to take me to a page where I can sign in. This used to use a different account system. Now it actually uses your K -State single sign -on account. So I’m going to go ahead and sign in to Azure using that account. It’s going to take me to my organization sign -in page. So I’ll sign in through K -State. It may need to do two factor if it needs to. And then it will pop in and take me to this page.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/4-directory-services/13-azurevms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/></channel></rss>