<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>July 20, 2020 :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200720/index.html</link><description>Resources Slides Video Script Good morning everyone and welcome to our week seven announcements video. I’m coming to you live and unscripted here from kind of a rainy Kansas City this morning. So let’s get right to it. First off, here’s where we’re at. Last Friday, lab five and six were due. So if you haven’t turned in and gotten graded for lab five and lab six, you should be doing so really quickly. Last I checked, I think we had maybe half the class done with lab five and a few people were through lab six. So hopefully we get that caught up very soon. Also, don’t forget the discussion response for week five, Ethan at Cerner, is due tomorrow. I apologize. I forgot to get the questions uploaded last week, but I uploaded them this morning. So that is available for you. So don’t forget to finish that discussion response by tomorrow. Today we have a special guest for our discussion. We have Dr. Gary Pratt. He is K-State’s CIO who’s going to be joining us and hopefully he’ll tell us a lot about K-State IT, the infrastructure we have at K-State, the future of IT at K-State, and kind of his top down perspective on how things are going. So I’m hoping that’s going to be a really good discussion. I hope you can join us. Lab seven. The last lab in this class is due this Friday, and we’ll discuss lab seven here in a bit. Also, don’t forget your proposals for the final project are due this Friday. So be thinking about your final projects if you haven’t done that. And lastly, a quick reminder, please make sure you check Calendly for our availability, both BreAnn and myself. BreAnn is starting a job next Monday and so her availability goes way down after this week. And actually toward the end of this week, it may be a little short. So please take a look at the calendly links for both BreAnn and I make sure you’re aware of our availability. And most most of the time I will be available, BreAnn will be available for parts of this week, but then starting next week will be much less available. So just be aware of that.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200720/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/></channel></rss>