




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Summer 2021 on CIS 527 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Summer 2021 on CIS 527 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>June 2, 2021</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210602/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210602/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week one announcements video for cis 527 in summer 2021, these announcements videos are usually much more unscripted than the other videos I do for this course. But I think it&amp;rsquo;s kind of fun to do these videos just so I can chat with you a little bit and tell you about what&amp;rsquo;s going on in the course. So once again, I&amp;rsquo;m Russell Feldhausen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>June 14, 2021</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210614/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210614/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week two announcements video for cis 527 in summer 2021. So this week, don&amp;rsquo;t forget today it&amp;rsquo;s Monday. So lab 1 is due by today at 7pm. However you do you need to schedule to have it graded and most of my grading times are before 5pm. So make sure if you haven&amp;rsquo;t done that yet, you need to schedule a time to grade ASAP on calendly so that I can meet with you via zoom and grade your lab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>June 21, 2021</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210621/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210621/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week three announcements video for CIS 527 in summer 2021. So we&amp;rsquo;re on week three, which means that lab do&amp;hellip; is lab two is due tonight at 7pm. So make sure you get that submitted, as we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about in a brief moment, the only things you have to submit on lab two are your two puppet manifest files. That&amp;rsquo;s all I need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>June 28, 2021</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210628/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210628/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week four announcements for cis 527 in summer 2021. I&amp;rsquo;m a bit informal this week because I decided not to set up all my recording equipment just to do my announcements this week, but I hope you can bear with me. So this week, we&amp;rsquo;ve got lab three, it&amp;rsquo;s due tonight by 7pm. This lab does require live grading. So if you haven&amp;rsquo;t scheduled a time to meet with me already, please do so as soon as you can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 6, 2021</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210706/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210706/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week five announcements video for cis 527 in summer 2021. So this week, you&amp;rsquo;ve got lab four, it&amp;rsquo;s actually due tomorrow, which is Wednesday by 7pm. So hopefully you&amp;rsquo;re getting things done with lab four. Also on Wednesday, you&amp;rsquo;ll have your question responses for last week&amp;rsquo;s discussion and the questions for this upcoming week&amp;rsquo;s discussion due that night by 11:59pm. Our speaker this week is Hunter Guthrie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 12, 2021</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210712/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210712/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week six announcements video for cis 527 in summer 2021. So at this point, you should be working on lab five, which is due tonight by 7pm. I see I&amp;rsquo;ve got meetings for most everybody already on my calendar. So that&amp;rsquo;s great. It looks like everybody&amp;rsquo;s keeping up so far. Then we&amp;rsquo;ve got our speaker coming up, we didn&amp;rsquo;t have a speaker last week, we&amp;rsquo;ve rescheduled Hunter to the week after this one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 19, 2021</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210719/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210719/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week seven announcements video for cis 527 in summer 2021. So we&amp;rsquo;ve only got two weeks left in the class, which means there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of stuff wrapping up this week. So don&amp;rsquo;t forget this week today Monday, your lab six is due by 7pm. Tonight, I see that again, most of you have already scheduled grading appointments, which is great.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 26, 2021</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210726/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/20210726/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week eight announcements video for cis 527 in summer 2021, here we are, it&amp;rsquo;s the last week of the class. This week, you should be working on lab seven, which is due tonight, it&amp;rsquo;s due by 11:59pm. And I&amp;rsquo;ll explain that in just a sec. We also have the week seven discussion response that&amp;rsquo;s due on Wednesday. So make sure you get that in.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>