<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Summer 2020 :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/index.html</link><description/><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>May 19, 2020</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200519/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200519/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to week one of CIS 527. This video is basically a weekly announcements video. I probably won’t do one each week, but it’s a good chance for me to describe a few things going on in the course and things that you may want to know as you get started. So first off, hopefully you’ve seen the introductory videos, but if not, my name is Russ Feldhausen. I’ll be your instructor for this semester. This slide has my contact information. Feel free to take a look at it and let me know. You can email me anytime although for things related to the class, I prefer that you contact me through through Piazza. That allows both myself and my GTA, BreAnn, to respond to those questions very quickly.</description></item><item><title>June 29, 2020</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200629/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200629/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week four announcements video. I’m really glad to be here once again, I am back in Kansas so I can finally do these videos from my home studio. First off some quick things hopefully by now you’re done with lab three, if not, you should be getting done with that pretty quickly. So if you haven’t yet scheduled a grading time with BreAnn or myself and we can get lab three taken care of. Also make sure you check out on Piazza we had some issues with SNMP and lab three. So if you’re struggling on the SNMP, part of lab three, there is some information on Piazza that will help you out with that. Also, don’t forget the week two discussion response, the first discussion that we had with Seth Galitzer, that is due today by midnight. All you have to do is answer the few questions I posted on Canvas and then upload your response to Canvas by midnight tonight. Then starting today at 4pm is the week three discussion where we have Adam and Kyle the two Beocat sysadmins coming to talk about how they work with a high performance computing infrastructure, such as Beocat, they always give really interesting talks, so I’m hoping everybody can make it. And then also, don’t forget, you should be starting on lab four. Generally lab four is regarded as one of the harder labs in this class, and it will be due next Monday.</description></item><item><title>July 7, 2020</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200706/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200706/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Good morning and welcome to the week five announcements video. I’m coming to you live and unscripted once again from my dining room just to cover a little bit about what’s going on this week in CIS 527. So first off, lab four, the due date was moved back one day, hopefully everybody saw that announcement last week. So it is now due tomorrow, which is Tuesday by 7pm. So hopefully either today or tomorrow, you’re ready to schedule a grading time with either BreAnn or myself. The week three response is still due today by 11:59pm. So make sure you get that in. Our week for discussion is also today at 4pm. We’re going to have some students from the Cyber Defense Club at K-State talking about their infrastructure that they use for training and getting ready for their cyber defense competitions. And then also be aware that lab five and lab six, we have grouped them together and both of them are due one week from Friday. That should be Friday. I believe it’s the 17th of July.</description></item><item><title>July 13, 2020</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200713/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200713/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Happy Monday morning I’m coming to you once again live and unscripted for our week six announcements video in CIS 527. I apologize for my Coronavirus hair. I haven’t gotten a haircut since March. So it’s definitely been interesting doing some of these videos and watching me change over the semester. I hope everybody’s doing well with the pandemic. I know it’s really tough right now. I’m living in Kansas City, and it’s really crazy right here. So I hope everybody’s staying safe and staying healthy.</description></item><item><title>July 20, 2020</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200720/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200720/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Good morning everyone and welcome to our week seven announcements video. I’m coming to you live and unscripted here from kind of a rainy Kansas City this morning. So let’s get right to it. First off, here’s where we’re at. Last Friday, lab five and six were due. So if you haven’t turned in and gotten graded for lab five and lab six, you should be doing so really quickly. Last I checked, I think we had maybe half the class done with lab five and a few people were through lab six. So hopefully we get that caught up very soon. Also, don’t forget the discussion response for week five, Ethan at Cerner, is due tomorrow. I apologize. I forgot to get the questions uploaded last week, but I uploaded them this morning. So that is available for you. So don’t forget to finish that discussion response by tomorrow. Today we have a special guest for our discussion. We have Dr. Gary Pratt. He is K-State’s CIO who’s going to be joining us and hopefully he’ll tell us a lot about K-State IT, the infrastructure we have at K-State, the future of IT at K-State, and kind of his top down perspective on how things are going. So I’m hoping that’s going to be a really good discussion. I hope you can join us. Lab seven. The last lab in this class is due this Friday, and we’ll discuss lab seven here in a bit. Also, don’t forget your proposals for the final project are due this Friday. So be thinking about your final projects if you haven’t done that. And lastly, a quick reminder, please make sure you check Calendly for our availability, both BreAnn and myself. BreAnn is starting a job next Monday and so her availability goes way down after this week. And actually toward the end of this week, it may be a little short. So please take a look at the calendly links for both BreAnn and I make sure you’re aware of our availability. And most most of the time I will be available, BreAnn will be available for parts of this week, but then starting next week will be much less available. So just be aware of that.</description></item><item><title>July 27, 2020</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200727/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200727/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Good morning and welcome to the last weekly announcements video for CIS 527 for summer 2020. I’m really excited to see the end of the semester and I hope you are too. Here’s a few quick things to keep in mind for this week. First off lab seven was due last Friday. So if you haven’t completed and turned in lab seven, make sure you do that ASAP. If you look on Piazza, there’s information about how to turn in lab seven completely offline so you don’t have to get any live grading done. But if you’re having trouble with it, you can always schedule a live grading time especially if you want us to look at what you’re doing and see if we can give you at least partial credit for it. So please make sure you do that. If you’ve already turned in lab seven, BreAnn went through and graded almost all of it this weekend. So hopefully you should see some notes on Canvas very shortly. If you haven’t heard back from her yet, you should be very soon. If you have gotten an email from her especially about task five on GitLab, please make sure you respond to that ASAP so that we can get the permissions we need so we can test task five of lab seven on GitLab. Also, don’t forget the final project proposal was due Friday, I believe I got a final project proposal from most everybody in the class. So that’s really great. I posted comments and feedback on those so you can check that out on Canvas anytime. Also, don’t forget the week six discussion response for Gary Pratt K-State CIO is due today. So you can go out to Canvas and find the discussion prompt for that. And also, final project presentations are coming up this week. So if you haven’t scheduled your time for your final project presentation, please do so now. My Friday afternoon is already almost completely booked up. So make sure you’re looking at my calendar and planning ahead accordingly. Just because you get it done on Friday doesn’t mean you may have time to present it if you haven’t scheduled a time, so don’t forget to do that. I generally prefer presentations on Thursday and Friday of this week. But if you think you’ll get done sooner you can schedule earlier than that. So check our Calendly availability and see when we’re available. Also, please bear in mind that BreAnn doesn’t have any official availability right; now she started her full time job this week. But she will be doing some stuff in the weekends and generally following up with this class when she has time. So mostly if you need Calendly availability, it will be on my calendar for the rest of this week.</description></item></channel></rss>