




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Summer 2020 on CIS 527 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Summer 2020 on CIS 527 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>May 19, 2020</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200519/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200519/index.html</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to week one of CIS 527. This video is basically a weekly announcements video. I probably won&amp;rsquo;t do one each week, but it&amp;rsquo;s a good chance for me to describe a few things going on in the course and things that you may want to know as you get started. So first off, hopefully you&amp;rsquo;ve seen the introductory videos, but if not, my name is Russ Feldhausen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>June 29, 2020</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200629/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200629/index.html</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week four announcements video. I&amp;rsquo;m really glad to be here once again, I am back in Kansas so I can finally do these videos from my home studio. First off some quick things hopefully by now you&amp;rsquo;re done with lab three, if not, you should be getting done with that pretty quickly. So if you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet scheduled a grading time with BreAnn or myself and we can get lab three taken care of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 7, 2020</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200706/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200706/index.html</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Good morning and welcome to the week five announcements video. I&amp;rsquo;m coming to you live and unscripted once again from my dining room just to cover a little bit about what&amp;rsquo;s going on this week in CIS 527. So first off, lab four, the due date was moved back one day, hopefully everybody saw that announcement last week. So it is now due tomorrow, which is Tuesday by 7pm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 13, 2020</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200713/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200713/index.html</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Happy Monday morning I&amp;rsquo;m coming to you once again live and unscripted for our week six announcements video in CIS 527. I apologize for my Coronavirus hair. I haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten a haircut since March. So it&amp;rsquo;s definitely been interesting doing some of these videos and watching me change over the semester. I hope everybody&amp;rsquo;s doing well with the pandemic. I know it&amp;rsquo;s really tough right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 20, 2020</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200720/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200720/index.html</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Good morning everyone and welcome to our week seven announcements video. I&amp;rsquo;m coming to you live and unscripted here from kind of a rainy Kansas City this morning. So let&amp;rsquo;s get right to it. First off, here&amp;rsquo;s where we&amp;rsquo;re at. Last Friday, lab five and six were due. So if you haven&amp;rsquo;t turned in and gotten graded for lab five and lab six, you should be doing so really quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 27, 2020</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200727/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/20200727/index.html</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Video Script Good morning and welcome to the last weekly announcements video for CIS 527 for summer 2020. I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to see the end of the semester and I hope you are too. Here&amp;rsquo;s a few quick things to keep in mind for this week. First off lab seven was due last Friday. So if you haven&amp;rsquo;t completed and turned in lab seven, make sure you do that ASAP.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>