<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Backups, Monitoring &amp; DevOps :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/index.html</link><description>Automatic deployment &amp; 99.9999% uptime.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:30:51 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/01-introduction/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/01-introduction/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Transcript Welcome to Module 7! In this module, we’ll discuss several additional topics related to system administration. Honestly, each of these items probably deserves a module unto themselves, if not an entire course. However, since I am limited in the amount of things I can reasonably cover in a single course, I’ve chosen to group these items together into this single module.</description></item><item><title>DevOps</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/02-devops/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/02-devops/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Extras - Git CS GitLab DevOps on Wikipedia Infrastructure as Code on Wikipedia What is DevOps? from Amazon Web Services What Is DevOps? from The Agile Admin DevOps: Breaking the Development-Operations Barrier from Atlassian Periodic Table of DevOps Tools from XebiaLabs The Ultimate DevOps Tool Chest from XebiaLabs webhook on GitHub webhook Hook Examples on GitHub Webhooks on GitLab Documentation Video Transcript One of the hottest new terms in system administration and software development today is DevOps. DevOps is a shortened form of “Development Operations,” and encompasses many different ideas and techniques in a single term. I like to think of it as the application of the Agile software development process to system engineering. Just as software developers are focusing on more frequent releases and flexible processes, system administrators have to react to quickly changing needs and environments. In addition, DevOps engineers are responsible for automating much of the software development lifecycle, allowing developers to spend more time coding and less time running builds and tests manually. Finally, to accommodate many of these changes, DevOps engineers have increasingly adapted the concept of “infrastructure as code,” allowing them to define their system configurations and more using tools such as Puppet and Ansible in lieu of doing it manually. As we saw in Module 2, that approach can be quite powerful.</description></item><item><title>ITIL</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/03-itil/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/03-itil/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides ITIL on Wikipedia ITIL from Axelos ISO/IEC 20000 on Wikipedia ISO/IEC 20000-1:2018 from ISO What is IT Service Management (ITSM) from Atlassian What is ITSM? Managing IT to serve business needs from CIO Video Transcript In this video, I’ll be taking a detour from all of the technical topics in this class to discuss a more philosophical topic: the art of system administration. Specifically, this video will introduce you to ITIL, one of the core resources for many IT organizations worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Assignment</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/04-assignment/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/04-assignment/index.html</guid><description>Lab 7 - Backups, Monitoring &amp; DevOps Instructions Create two cloud systems meeting the specifications given below. The best way to accomplish this is to treat this assignment like a checklist and check things off as you complete them.
If you have any questions about these items or are unsure what they mean, please contact the instructor. Remember that part of being a system administrator (and a software developer in general) is working within vague specifications to provide what your client is requesting, so eliciting additional information is a very necessary skill.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/05-monitoring/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/05-monitoring/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Best System Monitoring Tools for Windows &amp; Linux (Free &amp; Paid) from Comparitech Beocat System Monitor Video Transcript One major part of any system administrator’s job is to monitor the systems within an organization. However, for many groups, monitoring is sometimes seen as an afterthought, since it requires additional time and effort to properly set up and configure a monitoring system. However, there are a few good reasons to consider investing some time and effort into a proper monitoring system.</description></item><item><title>Windows Monitoring</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/06-windows-monitoring/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/06-windows-monitoring/index.html</guid><description>Resources Sysinternals Suite from Microsoft 11 Useful Tools for Windows SysAdmins from Anturis Blog Best System Monitoring Tools for Windows &amp; Linux (Free &amp; Paid) from Comparitech 20 Top Windows SysAdmin Tools You Should Know from Power Admin The Top 20 Free Network Monitoring and Analysis Tools for SysAdmins from GFI Tech Talk Top System Monitoring Tools for Windows Environments from PCWDLD Video Transcript In this video, I’m going to review some of the tools you can use to help monitor the health and performance of your Windows systems. While some of these tools support collecting data remotely, most of them are designed for use directly on the systems themselves. There are many paid products that support remote data collection, as well as a few free ones as well. However, since each one is unique, I won’t be covering them directly here. If you’d like to use such a system, I encourage you to review the options available and choose the best one for your environment.</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu Monitoring</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/07-ubuntu-monitoring/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/07-ubuntu-monitoring/index.html</guid><description>Resources 20 Command Line Tools to Monitor Linux Performance from TecMint 80 Linux Monitoring Tools from Server Density Blog System Monitoring Tools for Ubuntu from AskUbuntu Best System Monitoring Tools for Windows &amp; Linux (Free &amp; Paid) from Comparitech The Top 20 Free Network Monitoring and Analysis Tools for SysAdmins from GFI Tech Talk Seamless Infrastructure Monitoring from DigitalOcean Monitoring Quickstart from DigitalOcean How to Set Up Monitoring Alerts from DigitalOcean Video Transcript Ubuntu also has many useful tools for monitoring system resources, performance, and health. In this video, I’ll cover some of the more commonly used ones.</description></item><item><title>Backups</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/08-backups/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/08-backups/index.html</guid><description>Resources Slides Data Loss on Wikipedia 10 Common Causes of Data Loss from Consolidated Technologies Backup Types Explained: Full, Incremental, Differential, Synthetic, and Forever-Incremental from Nakivo Understanding RPO and RTO from Druva What is High Availability? from DigitalOcean Law Firm Retools its Backup Scenario from Network World Postmortem of Database Outage of January 31 from GitLab Video Transcript Backups are an important part of any system administrator’s toolkit. At the end of the day, no amount of planning and design can completely remove the need for high quality, reliable backups of the data that an organization needs to function. As a system administrator, you may be responsible for designing and executing a backup strategy for your organization. Unfortunately, there is no “one size fits all” way to approach this task, as each organization’s needs are different. In this video, I’ll discuss some different concepts and techniques that I’ve acquired to help me think through the process of creating a backup strategy.</description></item><item><title>Windows Backups</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/09-windows-backups/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/09-windows-backups/index.html</guid><description>Resources How to Back Up Windows 10 from Tech Advisor How to Use All of Windows 10’s Backup and Recovery Tools from HowTo Geek How to Make a Full Backup of your Windows 10 PC from Windows Central These resources mostly refer to Windows Server 2012 or 2016, but should work for 2019 as well.</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu Backups</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/10-ubuntu-backups/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/7-backups-monitoring-devops/10-ubuntu-backups/index.html</guid><description>Resources Backing Up Files from Ubuntu Documentation Backups from Ubuntu Server Guide How to Backup your Ubuntu Desktop with Déjà Dup from HowToForge Ubuntu 20.04 System Backup and Restore from Linuxconfig.org How to Compress and Extract Files using the tar Command on Linux from How-To Geek How to Import and Export Databases and Reset a Root Password in MySQL from DigitalOcean How To Backup MySQL Databases on an Ubuntu VPS from DigitalOcean (steps should still be valid for 20.04) Video Transcript There are many different ways to back up files and settings on Ubuntu. In this video, I’ll discuss a few of the most common approaches to creating backups on Ubuntu.</description></item></channel></rss>