<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Previous Semesters :: CIS 527 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/</link><description>Previous Semesters
Fall '23 Week 1 Summer '22 Week 1 Fall '23 Week 2 Fall '23 Week 3 Summer '22 Week 2 Fall '23 Week 5 Summer '22 Week 3 Fall '23 Week 8 Summer '22 Week 4 Fall '23 Week 9 Summer '22 Week 5 Summer '22 Week 6 Summer '22 Week 7 Summer '22 Week 8 Fall '23 Week 12 Summer 2020 May 19, 2020 June 29, 2020 July 7, 2020 July 13, 2020 July 20, 2020 July 27, 2020 Summer 2021 June 2, 2021 June 14, 2021 June 21, 2021 June 28, 2021 July 6, 2021 July 12, 2021 July 19, 2021 July 26, 2021 Fall 2021 Fall '21 Week 1 Fall '21 Week 3 Fall '21 Week 5 Fall '21 Week 9 Fall '21 Week 12 Fall 2021 Fall '22 Week 1 Fall '22 Week 3 Fall '22 Week 5 Fall '22 Week 7 Fall '22 Week 9 Fall '22 Week 11 Fall '22 Week 13 Fall '22 Week 14</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fall '23 Week 1</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week01/</guid><description>Ed Discussion This video was recorded before I decided to switch to Ed Discussion instead of using Discord. All discussions of “Discord” can be applied to “Ed Discussion” instead. Sorry for the confusion! - Russ
Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week one announcements for CIS 527 and CC 510. In Fall 2023, my name is Russ Feldhausen. I’ll be your instructor for this semester, my contact information can be found here.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 1</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week01/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week one Announcements video for system administration during summer 2022. My name is Russell Feldhausen. I’ll be your instructor for this course, my contact information is shown here. You can also find it on the syllabus and on the homepage on K-State canvas, it’s by far the best way to get a hold of me is to just email me. But as I discussed in the intro video, and as I’ll discuss here, for anything related to the course, please use discord, it’s a great place for us to chat and you should get some very quick responses from you there.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 2</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week02/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week two announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in Fall 2023. I’ll try and post announcements videos like this about every other week in this class. Usually these announcements videos are pretty informal, so you’ll notice I don’t have my background set up or anything, but it’s just a chance for me to talk through some things that are on my mind, things that I would normally announce at the beginning of class if we were meeting in person.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 3</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week03/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the Week Three announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in Fall 2023. So this week lab One is due tomorrow by 07:00 P.m., so make sure you get that done. Remember, for the lab grading, you need to schedule an interactive grading time with either Matt, My, UTA or myself via calendar. Both of our calendars are open. You can schedule a time anytime.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 2</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week02/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week two announcements video for CIS 527 in summer 2022. So this week you should be finishing up lab one. Lab one grading is due tonight by 7pm. So if you haven’t scheduled a time to meet with me for grading, make sure you do that ASAP. I do have trainings on Monday afternoons from about one to three, I usually get done with those a little earlier.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 5</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week05/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week five announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2023. This week we got a lot of stuff going on. We’ve got lab two that’s due on Wednesday, so tomorrow you should be getting done with lab two. There’s also the first discussion will be this Thursday, so the questions for our speaker for the first discussion are also due on Wednesday, so make sure you get those posted.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 3</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week03/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week three announcements video for CIS 527 in summer 2022. So this week you should be wrapping up lab two, which is due tonight at 7pm. I’ll talk about that briefly in just a second. You also should be working on the week two discussion questions and responses which are due tonight at 11:59pm. So make sure you leave enough time to watch that video, write your responses and respond to the question prompts there as well.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 8</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week08/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week eight announcements for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2023. So this week you should be wrapping up the second discussion. We had Adam come in and talk about his work on Beocat. So hopefully you’re getting a response put together for that. Also due tomorrow are the quizzes for Lab 4, so hopefully you’re getting those done. And then next week by Wednesday Lab 4 is due, so hopefully you’re able to get started working on that.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 4</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week04/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week for announcements video for CIS 527 in summer 2022. This week, you should be working on lab three, which is due today by 7pm. So make sure you getting that wrapped up and also that you have a time scheduled with me to get your grading done. I’ll talk about that in just a minute. You’re also should be working on the week three discussion, which is due tonight by 11:59pm.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 9</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week09/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week09/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the week nine announcements video for CIS 527 and CC 510 in fall 2023. This week Lab 4 is due tomorrow, so make sure you’re getting Lab 4 all wrapped up. Then you should also be starting on the content for Lab 5, which is some introduction to the cloud. And then a couple weeks from now you’ll have the Lab 5 content that’s actually due, so you should get started on Lab 5 sometime next week.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 5</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week05/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week five Announcements video for CIS 527 in summer 2022. So this week, you should be wrapping up lab four, which is notoriously the hardest lab in this class, it is due today by 7pm. So make sure you get that done and schedule a grading time with me later today. So we can get that looked at. And then next week, you’re going to be shifting over to lab five, where we’re going to pivot from virtual machines on our system to actually working in the cloud.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 6</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week06/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week six Announcements video for CIS 527 in summer 2022. So this week, you should be wrapping up lab five, which is due today at 7pm. So make sure you get that done. Most of lab grading is really simple. And we’ll talk about that in just a minute. You should also be wrapping up the week five discussion, which is also due tonight by midnight, so make sure you get that done.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 7</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week07/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the week seven announcements video for CIS 527 In summer 2022. So we’re getting toward the end of the semester. So this week, don’t forget you got lab six due tonight by 7pm. So make sure you get that submitted, I’ve got most grading times available for students. But if you need more help or needed writing time, just let me know.</description></item><item><title>Summer '22 Week 8</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2022/week08/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello, and welcome to the weekend Announcements video for CIS 527 In summer 2022. This week we should be wrapping everything up in the class. So you’ve got week seven discussion, which is due today by 1159. And then lab seven and the final project are due on Friday both by 1159. As well, you also should be receiving an email inviting you to complete a TEVAL for this course later today.</description></item><item><title>Fall '23 Week 12</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2023/week12/</guid><description>Resources Slides Video Script Hello and welcome to the Week 12 announcements video for CIS 527 in Fall 2023. As you can tell, I’ve been a little under the weather, so my voice is a little rough. I apologize for that. This week we’ve got a discussion three coming up with Sarah Allen. She’ll be here next Thursday, so please make sure you mark that on your calendar. You’ve got until next Wednesday to come up with a couple of questions.</description></item><item><title>Summer 2020</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2020/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Summer 2021</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/summer2021/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Fall 2021</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2021/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Fall 2021</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cis527/y-announcements/old/fall2022/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>